Finding Aid for James J. Duderstadt Papers 1963-1997
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Paper Documents
  - Speeches and Accompanying Material 1981-1996, 6.5 linear feet
    - 1987
      - Alumni Talk May 5, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Educating for a World of Change May 8, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Senate Assembly-5/18 May 17, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Welcome May 18, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Undergraduate Education May 31, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Undergraduate Enrollments June 9, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Conference on Industrial Competitivess (sic) June 16, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Development Staff June 30, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Business Administration September 17, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Senate Assembly September 24, 1987 (Box 22)
      - Western Michigan September 25, 1987 (Box 22)
      - West Quad October 25, 1987 (Box 22)
      - The Diversity Agenda 1.1 December 7, 1987 (Box 22)
    - 1988
      - Academic Affairs (Box 2)
      - Commencements (Box 2)
      - Michigan Mandate (Box 2)
      - Martin Luther King Event January 12, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Academic Affairs January 1988 (Box 2)
      - Medical Center Information Technology February 4, 1988 (Box 2)
      - SSC Testimony February 16, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Physics February 20, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Freshman Presentation February 22, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Future of Engineering February 22, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Graduate Education February 22, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Overheads: Challenge of Leadership: A Mission for the 21st Century March 12, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Traxler / Bloch March 14, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Leadership Evaluation March 14, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Undergraduate Education; Role of Alumni; Student-Athletes; State Legislature March 15, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Overheads: Challenge of Leadership: A Mission for the 21st Century March 28, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Overheads: Michigan Plan: A Strategy for the Enhancement of Excellence through Diversity March 28, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Questions April 11, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Science and Engineering Education for the 21st Century: Challenge of Change in Age of Knowledge April 15, 1988 (Box 2)
      - Alumni Talk, Philadelphia April 15, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Yale Science and Engineering April 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Overheads: A Challenge of Leadership: A Mission for the 21st Century April 19, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Plan; Viewgraphs; Version 1.2 April 22, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Ethics in Higher Education (Book) April 25, 1988 (Box 3)
      - College of Engineering Graduation April 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Public Service and the Public Research University April 1988 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Plan; Version 1.4; May 1, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Notes on Sculley May 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Educating for World of Change May 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Office of Academic Affairs Summary May 10, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Undergraduate Education Address May 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Fiscal Year 1988-89 Budget Presentation May 20, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Network Computing Forum Welcome May 25, 1988 (Box 3)
      - United States Department of Energy Visit Video May 31, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Brief History of State Capital Outlay Appropriations for Higher Education May 1988 (Box 3)
      - Athena Alumnae Award June 3, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Medical School Commencement June 3, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Science Foundation and Mich. Strategic Fund June 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Nursing Symposium June 11, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Freshman Convocation June 13, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Medicine-Computer II June 14, 1988 (Box 3)
      - IBM Dean's Conference June 14, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Blanchard-Tuition June 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Council on Academic Affairs Summer Retreat August 4, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Provost Keynote, San Diego August 8, 1988 (Box 3)
      - IFS Reception August 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Science Foundation Luncheon August 30, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Future's Talk September 2, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Mirlyn September 20, 1988 (Box 3)
      - If Harvard is the Michigan of the East... October, 1988 (Box 3)
      - State of the University October 3, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Inauguration October 4, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Historically Black, Predominately Hispanic Colleges October 5, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Faculty Awards and the Michigan Challenge October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Dean Kickoff Event October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - IFS Reception October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - National Science Foundation NET October 7, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Dedication of Canham Natorium October 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Hispanic Alumni October 21, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Booth Newspapers October 28, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Version 2.2 November, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Frankel Center for Judiac Studies November 1988 (Box 3)
      - Brass Hat Reception November 9, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Wilson Inauguration October 16, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Football Bust November 28, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Michigan Plan, Version 2.2 November, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
      - MLK Talks January 1988 (Box 22)
      - Athletes Reception February 7, 1988 (Box 22)
      - U.S. Department of Energy Public Hearing on SSC February 16, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Remarks March 8, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Welcome March 23, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Questions March 23, 1988 (Box 22)
      - The Michigan Plan March 24, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Undergraduate Education April 5, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Yale S&E Talk April 15, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Dean's Dinner April 24, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Remarks May 21, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Statement of James J. Duderstadt June 10, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Freshman Convocation September 6, 1988 (Box 22)
      - The Michigan Mandate-Senate Assembly September 19, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Congressional Delegation September 20, 1988 (Box 22)
      - General Talk September 22, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Leadership Network September 23, 1988 (Box 22)
      - The Challenge of Change October 6, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Alumni Talk October 12, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Prigogine December 9, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Thomas Kuhn December 9, 1988 (Box 22)
    - 1989
      - Major Presentations for 1989-1990 and List of Talks (Box 4)
      - Athletics (Box 4)
      - Commencements, May and December (Box 4)
      - Michigan Mandate, 2 folders (Box 4)
      - Set of Speeches (Box 4)
      - Lunch and Learn January 12, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Detroit Economics Club February 13, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Football Building Kickoff February 17, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Legislative / Alumni / Lansing March 14, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Honors Convocation March 19, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Native American Pow-Wow March 18, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Henry Russel Lecture March 21, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Continuity and Chaos March 24, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Women's Issues March 28, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Presidential Initiatives Fund Symposium March 28, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Legatus Talk March 30, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Team Building April 5, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Phi Beta Kappa April 8, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Satellite Broadcast April 9, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Basketball Bust April 10, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Senate Republican Caucus April 25, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Ann Arbor Rotary Club May 17, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Cal Tech Commencement June 16, 1989 (Box 4)
      - NAACP Convention September 8, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Corporate Program Remarks September 9, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Chemistry Building Dedication September 15, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Citizen's Research Council September 19, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Cleveland Lunch September 27, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Educom October 17, 1989 (Box 4)
      - State of the University October 2, 1989 (Box 4)
      - New York Business Leaders October 5, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Speech Topics December 3, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Tuition Press Conference December 3, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Women's Issues: An Agenda For Action March 28, 1989 (Box 22)
      - Continuity, Change, and Chaos April 8, 1989 (Box 22)
      - Preparing for a Future of Change June 16, 1989 (Box 22)
      - The Role of the Research University in Undergraduate Education September 26, 1989 (Box 22)
    - 1990
      - Set of Speeches (Box 4)
      - Michigan Mandate Two-Year Status Report (Box 4)
      - President's Council / Forums (Box 4)
      - Requests for Michigan Mandate (Box 4)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 4)
      - Speeches Pertaining to State Relations (Box 4)
      - Science Club Joint Lecture January 16, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Cranbrook February 11, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Congressional Delegation February 28, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Flint Rotary March 30, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Alumni Association Induction May 12, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Automotive Conference April 2, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Midland Adult Education April 5, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Alliance Conference April 6, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Democracy Symposium April 5, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Basketball Bust April 9, 1990 (Box 4)
      - United Way Leadership Conference April 9, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Senior Leaders Luncheon April 26, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Michigan Science and Technology Quest April 27, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Lamberto Cesari Memorial April 27, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Campus Information Center Meeting Welcome May 3, 1990 (Box 4)
      - English Commencement May 5, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Bo Farewell Dinner May 6, 1990 (Box 4)
      - President's Club / Spring Weekend May 18, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Ann Arbor Rotary May 15, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Service Awards Dinner June 6, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Hartford Memorial Baptist Church June 24, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Faculty Convocation September 24, 1990 (Box 4)
      - State of the University September 24, 1990 (Box 4)
      - Wallenberg Lecture September 25, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce September 26, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Ehrlicher Room Dedication October 4, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Michigan Ethnic Heritage Studies October 5, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Rackham Administration Office October 17, 1990 (Box 5)
      - Sante Fe Institute November 1, 1990 (Box 5)
      - AFL-CIO December 7, 1990 (Box 5)
      - America at the Crossroads: The Challenge of Science Education, Joint Meeting Science Research Club and Sigma Xi Scientific Research Society January 16, 1990 (Box 22)
      - A Heritage of Leadership: The Challenge of Change June 1, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Mandate: The Hope, Promise, and Challenge of Multicultural Society June 24, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Ann Arbor Chamber Commerce September 26, 1990 (Box 22)
      - The Michigan Mandate: To Build a Multicultural Learning Community for the 21st Century October 5, 1990 (Box 22)
      - Public Education in America: Crisis in an Age of Knowledge November 9, 1990 (Box 22)
    - 1991
      - Michigan Mandate Three-Year Status Report (Box 5)
      - Basketball Bust March 18, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Catholic Men's Breakfast April 2, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Junior League April 9, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Commencement May 4, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Senate Assembly May 20, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Forum on Educational Competitiveness May 20, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Class of 1995 Welcome September 1, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Freshman Parent Orientation September 1, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Graduate Convocation September 4, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Plymouth Northville Alumni October 3, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce October 15, 1991 (Box 5)
      - Ann Arbor Rotary October 30, 1991 (Box 5)
      - The Political Correctness Debate: Achieving a Balance Between Academics and Social Responsibilities May 20, 1991 (Box 22)
      - A Michigan Education September 27, 1991 (Box 22)
      - A Wake-Up Call to America October 15, 1991 (Box 22)
      - The External Environment of the University November 18, 1991 (Box 22)
    - 1991-1992
      - Sigma Xi / Science Research Club (Box 5)
      - Lansing Rotary January 24, 1992 (Box 5)
      - Public Service and the Public University August 1992 (Box 22)
      - Talking Points of James Duderstadt to Michigan Community College Presidents September 15, 1992 (Box 22)
      - Redrawing the Boundaries November 16, 1992 (Box 22)
    - 1993
      - Sigma Xi Scientific Research Society January 19, 1993 (Box 22)
      - A University Enterprise Zone February 9, 1993 (Box 22)
      - GM Volunteer Spirit Awards March 31, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Educating for the Age of Knowledge May 4, 1993 (Box 22)
      - A China Odyssey June 2, 1993 (Box 22)
      - Freshman Convocation September 1993 (Box 22)
      - Graduate Student Convocation September 8, 1993 (Box 22)
    - 1994
      - The University of the 21st Century May 23, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Introduction and Presentation of the Raoul Wallenberg Medal to His Holiness the Dalai Lama April 21, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Council on Continuous Improvement July 8, 1994 (Box 22)
      - New Student Convocation September 1, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Faculty Orientation Luncheon September 1, 1994 (Box 22)
    - 1995
      - Martin Luther King Day Opening Remarks January 16, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Introduction of Steven Olswang January 22, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Remarks for Symposium "Commitment to Collaboration: New Strategies for Community-Based Development in Detroit," February 2, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Parke-Davis presentation on Michigan Agenda for Women March 6, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Reinventing the University March 8, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Business to Business March 16, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Diversity and Excellence: The Challenge for a 21st Century World March 21, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Women: Transforming Higher Education Conference March 31, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Ann Arbor: An Economic Engine for the 21st Century April 6, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Salk Anniversary April 12, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Michigan Industrial Expo '95 April 11, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Jewish Federation Forum April 10, 1995 (Box 22)
      - President's Advisory Group, remarks May 5, 1995 (Box 22)
      - The Government-University Research Partnership: Beyond the Endless Frontier...? May 16, 1995 (Box 22)
      - 27th CIRP International Seminar on Manufacturing Systems, remarks May 22, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Dzero High-Energy Physics Collaboration Workshop June 12, 1995 (Box 22)
      - State of the University Address September 1995 (Box 22)
      - United Way Kick-Off Luncheon September 18, 1995 (Box 22)
      - A Vision for the 21st Century: Beyond "The Leaders and Best"... September 1995 (Box 22)
      - Outline for Senate Assembly September 25, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Rapid Changes in Business Technology: How Can Higher Education Help? November 21, 1995 (Box 22)
      - Groundbreaking for renovation of the University Health Service Building, remarks December 6, 1995 (Box 22)
    - 1996
      - Diversity January 1996 (Box 22)
      - Michigan's Future in a Word: Education February 2, 1996 (Box 22)
      - The Jerome B. Wiesner Symposium February 26, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Senate Assembly March 1996 (Box 22)
      - Commencement Address at University Graduate Exercises May 3, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Welcome comments for the 1996 Annual Meeting of the American Physical Society Division of Atomic, Molecular and Optical Physics, May 1996 (Box 22)
      - North American Manufacturing Research Conference May 22, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Speeches, not dated, 1 folders (Box 22)
      - Speech Engagements 1996 (Box 22)
      - Speech Schedule, ca. 1996 (Box 22)
  - Computer Printouts of Speeches 1988-1994, 3 linear feet
    Computer Printouts of Speeches (3 linear ft., 1988-1994) are printouts for the years 1988 to 1990 and 1992 to 1994. As such, they are often duplicates to the Speeches and Accompanying Materials series, but hold none of the contextual data. Most are dated, but there is no documentation as to whether this is a printout date or the date of creation. Researchers should note that many of the printouts are also available electronically, along with relevant data about them, in the Digital Documents subgroup. While this may on the surface seem redundant, preserving versions demonstrates some of the ways Duderstadt's office functioned, particularly in the evolving years of electronic record keeping. It becomes evident when the paper series are considered alongside the digital versions, that Duderstadt's office became over the years, more and more committed to functioning wholly in the electronic realm. Finally, since the papers were not processed at an item level, keeping these diverse versions offers the best likelihood that the collection will fairly comprehensively hold most of Duderstadt's speeches for this period.
    - 1988-1989
      - Parent's Orientation September 4, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Leadership Network September 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Leadership Network (b) September 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Graduate Student Welcome September 8, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Minority Students Welcome September 8, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Dean / Executive Officers Kickoff 2.0 September 11, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Fall Weekend September 23, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Rackham 50th (a) September 30, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Rackham 50th (b) September 30, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Faculty Awards October 3, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Historically Black Colleges and Universities Remarks October 5, 1988 (Box 5)
      - "Home" October 5, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Student Inaugural Address October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Student Inauguration 1.5 October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration 1.2 October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration 1.3 October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Inauguration Remarks List October 6, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Medical Center Reception October 17, 1988 (Box 5)
      - 3-M Visit October 18, 1988 (Box 5)
      - UM-Flint Science Bldg Dedication October 20, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Alumni Talk - Short October 22, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Leadership Network October 28, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Booth Newspapers October 29, 1988 (Box 5)
      - New Detroit Presentation November 3, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Judaic Studies November 15, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Medical Education November 21, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Football Bust November 28, 1988 (Box 5)
      - Commencement December 18, 1988 (Box 5)
      - UM-Flint Commencement December 22, 1988 (Box 6)
      - Big Ten Championship December 29, 1988 (Box 6)
      - Listen and Learn Talk January 12, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Unity March January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Opening January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Science / Manpower January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Business & Finance January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Martin Luther King Day - Closing January 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - CBS Good Morning Show February 3, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Detroit Economic Club (a) February 13, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Detroit Economic Club (b) February 13, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Dedication of Canham Natatorium February 17, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Congressional Breakfast March 1, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Legislature March 14, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Pow-Wow '89 March 18, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Honors Convocation March 19, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Women's Issues March 28, 1989 (Box 6)
      - PIF Remarks March 28, 1989 (Box 6)
      - IPPS Welcome March 29, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Legatus Talk March 30, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Mortar Board April 1, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Student Recognition Awards April 3, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Welcome Home April 4, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Penn State April 6, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Phi Beta Kappa April 8, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Alumni Satellite Breakfast April 9, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Basketball Bust (a) April 10, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Basketball Bust (b) April 10, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Coaches Reception April 19, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Senate Appropriations April 24, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Senate Republican Caucus April 25, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Commencement-- Rain April 29, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Commencement - Spring April 29, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Coaches Talk May 3, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Rotary Club May 17, 1989 (Box 6)
      - President's Weekend May 19, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Leadership Network May 21, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Cal Tech Commencement June 16, 1989 (Box 6)
      - Undated
        (arrived at library filed with 1988-1989)
        - Research Excellence Fund (Box 6)
        - International Issues (Box 6)
        - Commitments for Speeches (Box 6)
        - Cost of Higher Education (Box 6)
        - Undergrad Education (Box 6)
        - Campaign Discussion (Box 6)
        - Congressional Delegation (Box 6)
        - National Association University State Land Grant Colleges, San Diego (Box 6)
        - Investments (Box 6)
        - Future Talk 1.0 (Box 6)
        - IFS Reception (Box 6)
        - National Science Foundation Luncheon (Box 6)
        - Blanchard - Tuition (Box 6)
        - Luncheon (Box 6)
        - Volunteer Leadership (Box 6)
        - Development Leadership (Box 6)
        - General Talk (Box 6)
        - Michigan Mandate (Box 6)
        - Alumni Talk (a) (Box 6)
        - Alumni Talk (b) (Box 6)
      - Other Speech Printouts, 9 folders (Box 6)
      - Other Speech Printouts, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - 1992-1993
      - Rose Bowl 1992 (Box 7)
      - Martin Luther King Day January 20, 1992 (Box 7)
      - Parent's Weekend November 15, 1992 (Box 7)
      - Grand Rapids Rotary December, 1992 (Box 7)
      - Rose Bowl 1993 (Box 7)
      - Martin Luther King Day January 18, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Mandate Regents Meeting January 21, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Harold Johnson Retirement January 27, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Lunch and Learn February 9, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Graduating Minority Students March 26, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Alumni Club Detroit April 13, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Sam Wu Memorial April 1993 (Box 7)
      - President's Advisory Group June 3, 1993 (Box 7)
      - New Students Convocation September 7, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation May 10, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Custodial Appreciation August 30, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Perrin Chair September 10, 1993 (Box 7)
      - South Wayne Chamber September 20, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Hill Auditorium September 30, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Renick Inauguration October 1, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Whitaker Portrait October 1, 1993 (Box 7)
      - President's Weekend October 11, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Parke-Davis October 8, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Tanner Lecture October 22, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Hatcher Birthday October 22, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Go Blue Brunch October 23, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Press Club November 15, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Parent's Weekend Tailgate November 6, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Senate Assembly November 15, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Mellon Foundation January 10, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Martin Luther King Day January 10, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Sigma Xi January 18, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Prechter Lab February 5, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Alumni Club Detroit February 8, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Holocaust Dedication March 13, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Pow-Wow March 25, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Bob Forman Retirement April 28, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Quarterback Club May 9, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Rhetaugh Dumas May 10, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Portland Talk May 16, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Bob Forman Reception May 18, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Weidenbach Luncheon and Dedication May 20, 1994 (Box 7)
      - President's Advisory Group June 2, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Alumni Day June 18, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Service Awards June 15, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Zuidema Retirement Reception June 17, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Congressional Reception June 28, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Position Papers 1984-1991, 0.25 linear feet